Straighten your shoulders, breathe.
Don't bend.
Hey, get up, get up!
Got up.
Deep breath, asshole.
- Hurt?
- It hurts, so stop it.
That's enough.
Get it!
Rise.
Move away. To the side.
Jeongwon.
Lately I have
There is no force in the blow, right?
Jerk.
I'll be quick.
Don't rock the boat, you know that right?
Dodged!
Jongwon dodged.
Hey, did you dodge?
Look at him.
Unhook.
Take your hands off.
Get your hands off you asshole!
- I'll break it!
- Namhyup!
Kim Namhyup!
Who else is this?
Who is Kim Namhyup from Seomun School?
That's where he's hiding.
Who are you?
We are high school heroes.
Toot-dong!
Let's go!
OK.
Who are you anyway?
Forward.
What? Does it hurt when they hit you?
What scum!
Get up, freak.
Hurt?
Go get some rest.
Stand still!
Well done!
You won't catch it, idiot!
I'm telling you, you won't catch it!
How quirky.
Hurt?
Get some rest.
Know your limits.
ABOUT! Fanservice!
Fine.
This is fan service.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! That's enough, damn it.
You'll torture the guy.
Namhyup.
So what does it feel like?
Dude, take a video of him.
Buddy.
Come here.
Go, go.
Namhyup.
Sincerely apologize to this guy.
If I don't feel sincerity -
you'll get it one more time.
Who are you?
Apologize!
Hands off!
Take your hands off and apologize, damn it.
Sorry.
Oh, it's crazy, really.
Hey, look him in the eyes and say:
"Please forgive me."
Really, it's so annoying, really, damn it.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Listen, friend.
Well, can you forgive?
Do you know what forgiveness is?
This is not an obligation, but a right.
No one can demand
forgiveness from the victim.
This is not possible.
If you don't want to -
you don't have to forgive.
And those who say that, having forgiven,
you are healing...
this is all bullshit.
This was invented by those who
there are even more sins behind the soul.
Complete nonsense, you know?
The real way to heal is
is to punch those who hit you,
exactly the same.
Erase the fear you felt
when I couldn't fight back,
that's what heals.
These guys...
Now they definitely won't touch you.
Do you know why?
Because I will post a video on the Internet,
which my friend is filming.
In general, boy
hit those who hit you in the same way.
Understood? You can do it, try it.
Can you pull yourself together, okay?
Cool!
Wow, wow!
Friend...
These guys aren't that scary
as you think.
Now always
let's fight back, okay?
Don't be afraid of those
believe in us, in those who
believes in you, understand?
Don't be a coward, don't piss anymore! These assholes...
Oh, what vile types, aren't they?
Really... How disgusting you are, damn it.
Oh, wait.
Are you really
Is this your first time trying beer?
I?
Hey, last week I...
Chivas 38 years old
I made one pile
with grandfather.
Yes, you can't compare with the rich.
Oh, exactly...
Send me the video you took.
Send to Choi Jongwon.
For him it will be like, some kind of, you know...
Condition? Reward? Well, something like that.
So that when things get difficult for him,
he could watch it and gain strength.
- Has it arrived?
- Yes.
Jerk.
I didn't think that Kim Namhyup
it will shake so much.
It was even ridiculous.
OK.
Weren't you hurt?
I? Of course not, what about you?
Yes, everything is fine with me,
as if I was playing with toys.
Nothing.
Bullshit!
Listen, you're a quick learner of fan service.
Yes, you gave a great speech.
- Is it true?
- Yes.
It worked out well.
Listen, when I said...
it was like,
bring justice.
It really felt like that.
Everything in my chest was so tight, it was so cool.
I almost burst into tears myself,
wow, that was something, really.
In general,
congratulations to high school heroes
Happy debut!
- Loyalty!
Listen, carry all this junk
not cool at all.
And yours too.
Again he is on his own.
Listen, are you true?
won't you eat with me and leave?
I'm hungry, so I'll give you a treat, okay?
I made an agreement at the academy,
so they don't call your father.
Classes are ending now.
It's late, I'm leaving.
I'm hungry. Well, this is too much, really.
Kim Namhyup, raise your head.
Take your hands off, damn it.
Raise your head and apologize normally.
Sorry. Please forgive me.
Do you remember his voice?
Me yesterday
brought this asshole to his knees.
And I will force the rest to kneel.
Time's up!
Everyone put down your pens!
Back row, collect answers.
Put down your pens.
Put it down!
Try the same in the next exam.
Yes!
How many unfamiliar questions were there?
Was there anything difficult there?
What a weirdo.
Well written?
I never look back
for past tasks.
I only think about tomorrow.
I chose my next goal.
The exam is over, let's go.
Seungjun.
Chihyuk told you to come.
I told you I quit the game.
If you don't go today,
It will be worse for you.
Chihyuk is very angry.
I'll try to talk to him
come with me after school for a while.
I need to go to the gym right after school.
I'm boxing again.
If I get punished again because of you,
then I will kill you.
Me too?
Leave him alone
who decided to take up sports.
Oh, damn.
Hey.
Tell Choi Chihyuk,
so that he doesn't touch Seungjoon anymore.
I warned you.
Oh, cool said.
Went.
Hey.
I'm glad you're boxing again.
You know?
Choi Chihyuk and Nam Seungsik
They weren't such idiots in the first place.
They became like this
when they realized that they were strong.
You are the same now.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
I'm worried that you are too
you'll become such an idiot.
It was a difficult decision for us too.
Yes.
You can promise
that you will behave well?
I promise.
You...
Remember this is your last chance.
I remember.
Try your best.
Thank you.
What again? He was pardoned.
Mom told me to study.
Well, take a walk once.
Well, that's not interesting.
I'm telling you, you can skip it.
Yeah, what an atmosphere.
Who is this new guy?
This is Nam Seungsik's place.
I need to tell him.
What's happened?
Why are you gathered here?
Move away.
Aw.
Who are you?
New guy?
Yeah.
Crap.
What's happened?
One hat is gone
and a Panama hat was drawn?
I have my reasons.
The director gave me permission.
Is it true?
Could you please leave?
This is my place.
Sorry.
I thought the place was free.
Everything is fine.
Anything can happen.
But if you're sorry,
lend me some money.
Otherwise I'm broke now.
I have a lot of places to spend it.
Help those in need.
Is this enough?
And we'll get along.
Then I'll ask you a favor.
I want to live in peace.
Can you help me?
Is it true?
OK.
Then pay me 100 thousand won a week.
If you don't have money,
work it out with your body.
Crap.
Are you kind of cool too?
Got it.
Crap.
And you're annoying.
Let's finish.
Please.
It won't work.
I'm in a mood today
very shitty.
Lee Gwije!
On the first day
transferred and immediately fight?
You...
Know that you are lucky.
Nam Seungsik, Lee Gwije, both of you...
Go to the teachers' room now.
Assholes.
Hey, go to class.
Aren't you coming? Run!
Crap.
Seriously...
Hey Hongil.
Yes?
Are you okay?
Yes, everything is fine.
Sorry.
I almost died because of you.
What does the guy look like
who left the colony?
You will understand if you see him.
Eugyom.
They say a student has been transferred to third grade
and got into a fight with Nam Seungsik.
- Why?
- In terms of?
It's obvious that he wants to take over the school.
If he kills Nam Seungsik,
then you'll be next.
Where to go?
Wait.
There is no need to fight right away.
You need to study it first.
Let's go now.
OK.
Straightaway?
New kid here from high school?
I recognized it right away.
I heard about you, so I came.
If you want to take over the school,
then you had to find
Kim Uigyeom, not Nam Seungsik.
Let's talk in a quiet place.
Are you really Gwije from Mumyeon School?
There was a misunderstanding.
I don't want to fight.
Then why did you fight with Nam Seungsik?
I was just defending myself.
Then protect yourself from me too.
Hey Eugyeom!
No need, this is not your opponent.
- Move away.
- Listen to me, hey.
Let's fight later.
Please.
I told you
that I'm not going to fight.
Do not touch me.
If I fight, you will die.
I'm serious.
Wait.
I've heard about you since middle school.
I apologize for today's incident.
We didn't want to fight, we just...
We thought you did too
you like to fight like bullies.
I'm sorry.
Than your actions
different from bullies?
They are different.
- We only beat up bad guys.
- Calm down.
It's funny.
Who decides who is bad?
Am I good or bad?
And you?
Those who wave their fists
usually a bad ending.
You have to experience it to understand.
You will understand this yourself one day.
Wow!
I almost shit myself seeing him live.
Madness.
Is he that strong?
Even if it's ten
Kim Yygemov - useless.
When everyone knows who he is,
won't stay at school
not a single show-off.
The school will become quiet.
That's why strength is needed.
So...
they didn't fight?
Yes.
This new one...
said he had no desire to fight.
What?
Why are they suddenly...
show respect for other people's feelings?
Seungsik,
are you funny?
Rumors spread around the school
that you were rebuffed by a first-year student.
Is it true?
And about the fact that he got you off?
first year, haven't you heard?
Moomyeon School?
Yes, this is the school I'm talking about
almost no one knows.
This is a kind of experimental school,
very problematic place.
Teenage delinquency
crossed the line.
In juvenile detention centers
can't cope.
When in one place
only hooligans are gathered,
they get even worse.
Isn't it?
Therefore, children need to be reformed,
and not produce repeat offenders.
Therefore, the Ministry of Education...
created an experimental school.
There are several such schools throughout the country.
It’s not like it’s a colony, but it’s not a school either...
In any case, the teachers there...
rather create an atmosphere of competition.
They rank the kids based on their fighting skills.
- Do you know about Samcheon Training Camp?
- Yes.
They drove them there
and were treated like dogs.
Imagine it's the same.
But at Mumyeon school you need
fight every day.
You can't help but fight.
If you can't fight,
then you will live like a complete slob.
The fact that Gwidzhe
transferred to a regular school means...
that he came out of Mumyeon in charge.
If you're in charge there,
you can transfer.
That's why they fight so hard.
Understood?
Oh damn, hey!
This is Gwidzhe!
If he is on our side...
then we had nothing
would be afraid in this world.
What's going on here?
- Grab this bastard!
- Hey, let's go!
Wow, cool, hey!
Eygyom, let's go have a look! Quickly, let's go!
Hey, let's take a look, quickly!
Quickly, quickly, come here!
Hey!
What?
Were you waiting for me?
Do you really need this?
Impressive.
Still a legend of the Mumyeon school.
I didn't know you were so famous.
How about...
play a game with me?
I'm speaking for the last time.
I'll be as quiet as a mouse.
Let's finish this.
What charisma!
But it's too late.
It's about my pride.
Whoever crosses is a corpse.
Steep.
What are you doing? I'm not finished yet.
Let's get this over with.
Get out of the way.
If you want to live.
Gwidzhe!
Wait!
Wow, you really are a legend, huh?
Once again I apologize for
what happened earlier.
That guy...
looked dangerous.
You know this too, right?
Don't just look at him in a bad way.
You said it yourself.
Need to experience it.
We are also currently in the process of testing.
But you don't want to get into trouble.
If rumors of a fight spread
at school, you will have problems.
I filmed it.
If I ever need help,
could you help just once?
Are you blackmailing me now?
No, no, no, this is negotiation.
So you owe me now, okay?
Just one time, okay?
2/4 minus 3t…
Multiply...
It's funny.
Who decides who is bad?
Am I good or bad?
And you?
Now you need to take
derivative t for each
Then...
3t squared plus...
You failed your midterms.
I called the academy and guess what?
You were always late
and now he’s stopped walking altogether?
Kim Eugyom.
Forgot who you are?
What are you even doing, huh?
Not answering?
Stop it!
Why are you hitting the child?
You can ask first.
Why did he do this, what does he do?
I'm asking.
Can't we talk without assault?
Don't interfere.
He doesn't understand words!
Let's stop this
forced training.
Enough already.
What an excellent student will be
skip classes at the academy?
Your teaching method...
Don't you think that he
only spoils the child?
What?
Because of your teaching method...
He's only getting worse!
Enough.
Stop it.
Hey.
You said you would bring it, didn’t you?
Do you want to make me angry?
No.
You said you would lend me money.
Did he speak or not?
He spoke.
Am I a beggar, huh?
I have no money?
You said you would bring it today!
That's why I didn't take any money with me!
But you say you have no money.
What should I do today then, huh?
Sorry, Kiyun.
I'll definitely bring it tomorrow.
Not tomorrow, but today!
What the hell should I do today?
Why don't they give him the money?
What do they want to do
since Li Kiyun was called?
- Exactly.
- Sorry.
Go get involved.
What can I do?
Damn Lee Kiyun...
Hey, the fat guy is cute, isn't he?
- He has such shoulders!
- I'm going to throw up.
Is he your boyfriend?
What are you talking about?
Those are fat people!
The skin is so soft
If you hit it, your lips will immediately break.
And you can't beat him.
Stand up straight!
Stand up straight, motherfucker, stand up straight!
Angry!
I'm filming!
You come here too.
Damn it!
I'm embarrassed in front of the girls now.
Frenzy.
Send it to me.
Stand up straight.
Funny, right?
Hey.
Did I ask you to bring it?
You said you would bring it!
Stop mocking the weak.
If you don't have money, come to us.
- What the hell is this?
- Do you know him?
What do you need?
We'll make you laugh.
Let's go?
What the hell are these bastards!
- Get out.
- Yes.
Who are you anyway?
- What, do you want to take it off?
- We need to take it off.
- Get up.
- Got up!
Who are you, huh?
Crap!
I'm hungry.
Me too.
Get up, Li Kiyun!
I have to wash it all, damn it!
Everything is fine?
Who are we?
High School Heroes,
who punish the bad guys.
Hey buddy.
Bitches!
I will kill you!
- More.
- Fighting is innate.
Strike again.
Hit!
Cool!
Nice!
That's it.
Get up.
Get up and strike!
You like to hit children.
I will kill you today, just like you!
What are you doing?
Get up.
Where are you crawling?
You mock the weak
and think that you are a king?
Have mercy.
What?
Fine.
I'll spare you.
Stop it!